export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Solidity is a ____",
    options: ["programming Language", "blockchain", "syntax", "solid mineral"],
    answer: "programming Language"
  },
  {
    question: "What does EVM stands for?",
    options: ["Entourage Virtual Machine", "Ethereum Vesting Machine", "Ethereum Virtual Machine", "Electronic Voting Machine"],
    answer: "Ethereum Virtual Machine"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the founder of Ethereum",
    options: ["Vitalik Satoshi", "Vitalik Buterin", "Nick Szabo", "Rick Jones"],
    answer: "Vitalik Buterin"
  },
  {
    question: "The Turing machine was invented in 1936 by",
    options: ["Gavin Wood", "Bill Gate", "Kleene Rice", "Alan Turing"],
    answer: "Alan Turing"
  },
  {
    question: "Ethereum utilizes its native cryptocurrency called ",
    options: ["Ether(ETH)", "Ethereum(ETH)", "Ethernaut(ETH)", "Ether Tether(ETH)"],
    answer: "Ether(ETH)"
  },
  {
    question: "Which consensus mechanism is Ethereum currently using",
    options: ["Proof Of Work (POW)", "Proof Of History (POH)", "Proof Of Stake (POS)", "Proof Of Authority (POA)"],
    answer: "Proof Of Stake (POS)"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of gas fees in Ethereum?",
    options: ["To speed up the internet", "To pay miners and validators for processing transactions", "To store data permanently on the blockchain", "To prevent blockchain hacks"],
    answer: "To pay miners and validators for processing transactions"
  },
  {
    question: "Which token standard is used for fungible tokens on Ethereum?",
    options: ["ERC-20", "ERC-721", "ERC-1155", "ERC-777"],
    answer: "ERC-20"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the smallest unit of Ether (ETH) called?",
    options: ["Gwei", "Finney", "Wei", "Szabo"],
    answer: "Wei"
  },
  {
    question: "Which token standard is used for non-fungible tokens on Ethereum?",
    options: ["ERC-20", "ERC-721", "ERC-1155", "ERC-777"],
    answer: "ERC-721"
  }
]